

# Azadeh Hakkak

Junior Web Developer

## **MY BACKGROUND**

After being a Makeup Artist for 16 years and all the great things that I've learned I got to a point that it was time for a new challenge. So i decided to take a brave decision and become a software engineer as it involves both creativity and logic. During my course I learned that nothing is impossible and we can achieve whatever we want with hard work and a curious mind. Life is too short to do anything that's not challenging.

## **MY JOB SKILLS**

- lavaScript
- HTML/CSS
- Ruby on Rails/Ruby
- Reac
- Git
- jQueryNode.js
- Sales Skills
- Customer Service
- Accurate Data Entry
- Leadership
- Time Management

## **SOFTWARE ENGINEERING PROJECTS**

- Tic -Tac -Toe: Simple Game made using:
  - Javascript/jQuery/HTML / CSS
  - Link: https://azihakkak.github.io/tictactoe/
- Inkt: A website for connecting Tattoo Artists around the world to share ideas, made using:
  - Ruby on Rails/Bootstrap/HTML/CSS
  - Link: https://deployerinkt.herokuapp.com/
- MarkT (Group Project): An application for companies to follow up their E-commerce Campaigns, made using:
  - React front-end with bootstrap, Ruby on Rails back-end server connecting through AJAX
  - Link: https://campaign-ads-markt.netlify.app/
- GlamB: A website for booking and managing different makeup services, made using:

   React front-end with Bootstrap, communicating to Ruby on Rails back-end server via AJAX
   Link: https://priceless-wilson-b264e7.netlify.app

#### **CONTACT DETAILS**

Email : azadeh.hakkak@gmail.com Linkedin URL:https://www.linkedin.com/in/azadehhakkak Portfolio Link: https://Azihakkak.github.io/Portfolio GitHub Link: https://github.com/Azihakkak

## **CAREER HISTORY**

Counter Manager - YSL Cosmetics David Jones, Jul 2019- Feb 2020

2IC/ Sales Representative - Chanel Cosmetics David Jones, Nov 2018- Jul 2019

Counter Manager - Laura Mercier Cosmetics David Jones, Dec 2017 - Nov 2018

2IC/ Sales Representative - Lancome Cosmetics David Jones, Feb 2014 - Dec 2017

#### **COMMON TASKS**

- Managed weekly inventory
- · Ensured cash was managed efficiently
- Implemented strategies to minimize store costs and ultimately raise profit
- Greet and assist customers as they shop for new products
- Banking,data entry
- Evaluates customer's needs and promote products and services
- Train and supervise a team of 3 in-store employees
- Prepare and submit weekly sales reports to management

## **EDUCATION & TRAINING**

General Assembly Sydney

Software Engenieering-Immersive, 2020

Islamic Azad University

Bachelor of Arts-English Translation, 2004-2008

Certificate in advanced Makeup from Lancôme (year 2016)

Certificate I&II in Makeup from Lancôme (year 2015)

Certificate in Makeup artistry (year 2007)

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Certificate I&II in Makeup from Lancôme with top score
- L'Oréal L.U.X Accredited sales & service provider
- Lancôme Makeup Artist runner up of the year 2016
- Participation in Makeup for Mercedes Benz Fashion
- Attended the International Lancôme Makeup event 2016 in New Zealand as a Makeup instructor and Makeup artist
- Part of Mercedes Benz 2017 fashion week makeup team